This is Henry.
He weighs 90 kilos, and he's about to
CONQUER ROME.
Yes, that Rome. Sometimes referred to
as the Everlasting City,
which sounds impressive,
but it's been sacked six times.
The difference is that Henry is planning
on doing it with 79 men...
80 men. I didn't see
that sneaky bastard.
You probably want to know how...
uh, but that's not important!
What is important is why.
You see, Henry is in love with Loretta,
(pictured here)
but her father,
will only let her marry a man
that can prove he can provide,
which, in this time period, meant a great warrior...
or a... person that can grow a turnip.
Picking at random, Henry chose the more...
unhealthy challenge...
and to prove that he's a great warrior,
he wanted to conquer a city.
Why he picked Rome,
a city who's conquerability has historically
been described as...
"VERY INCONVENIENT", we may never know.
Maybe he picked the European capital
with the least amount of letters.
Maybe he was getting some authentic
Italian food and thought,
"Oh, while I'm in the neighborhood..."
Most likely he just underestimated its
size and defenses,
for example, what you are seeing right now.
Well I'm sorry to disappoint you,
but back in 400 A.D. Rome, they did
not have rocket engines.
That is what the Romans refer to as
which directly translates to:
You might be worried that one of the
rocks might hit our protagonist,
but they won't.
They will, instead, hit his best friend, Jerry.
...who was against this invasion from the start,
but, because of his strict father, had confidence
issues and never spoke up.
I'm sure he would be regretting that right now...
if he wasn't decomposing.
This is Claudius.
a Roman General, and a noble,
so he has been educated in math.
That means he would be able to calculate
that one giant rock equals a big pile of money,
and one Saxon soldier equals NOT a big pile of money.
Mistaking Henry's cowardice for military brilliance,
he will surrender, and give up the city.
Good job, Saxon boys!
At least, uh, that was Henry's plan,
but that's... not actually what happened...
This is Henry.
He weighs 90.06 kilos.
The extra weight comes from
the 6 arrowheads that has entered his body,
and, according to medical journals, being
penetrated by six arrows
means it's very likely he is dead.
Which would be sad,
but the truth is, Henry's life was just one
big disappointment after another,
so it's, uh... ehhh.